<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chapters on Night Tripper</title>
    <link>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chapters on Night Tripper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Foreward</title>
      <link>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/foreward/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/foreward/</guid>
      <description>Foreward Night Tripper is a starting point. A set of light and modular tools, rules and procedures. Use them as written only as long as they serve your shared goals. Hack, expand, and repurpose them without hesitation. They assume a group of three or more, with one person acting as Referee and the others as players controlling individual characters.
Night Tripper is not original. If you are familiar with the earliest 2d6 interstellar role-playing games, you&amp;rsquo;ll recognize a lineage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Features</title>
      <link>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/coming-soon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/coming-soon/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming Features Priorities Planned additions to Night Tripper, coming soon.
 Tables of example trade goods in each category More insider and outsider encounters Example VIPs Example opportunities An example star map to launch or inspire your campaign  Musings Potential features, down the road a ways.
 Automated character generator? Automated star map generator? An editor?  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inspirations</title>
      <link>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/inspirations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://night-tripper.netlify.app/chapters/inspirations/</guid>
      <description>Inspiration Role-playing:  Traveller, by Marc Miller Troika, by Daniel Sell Into the Odd, by Chris McDowall Tunnel Goons by Nate Treme Pacts &amp;amp; Blades by Lucas Rolim Luke Gearing&amp;rsquo;s blog  Novels:  Consider Phlebas by Iain M. Banks Ancillary Justice by Ann Leckie Ninefox Gambit by Yoon-Ha Lee  Illustration &amp;amp; Painting:  Science fiction characters by Alain Gruetter Paintings by John Harris  Music This eclectic and growing Spotify playlist I made.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
